(Scene:)Sheldon.
(Scene:)- Sheldon.
- Danger. Danger.
No danger, it's me, Penny.
Listen, I got to level 25
and reached Purple Lotus Swamp, right?
- You're in my bedroom.
- Yeah.
(Penny:)- Leonard gave me an emergency key.
- People can't be in my bedroom.
(Penny:)- Can we go talk in the living room?
- I'm not wearing pajama bottoms.
(Man:)- Why not?
- I spilled grape juice.
Well, wear different pajamas.
Can't wear different pajamas.
These are my Monday pajamas.
(Sheldon:)Penny, people cannot be in my bedroom.
(Penny:)Just tell me, is it too soon
to join a quest to the Black Castle?
(Sheldon:)You were invited on a quest
to the Black Castle?
(Penny:)By some guys in Budapest. I'm just not
sure it's the right move for my character.
(Sheldon:)Of course it's not. You're only a level 25.
These Hungarians are just using you
for dragon fodder.
(Penny:)Really? Boy, you'd think you could trust
a horde of Hungarian Barbarians.